So, thank you very much for joining us today in Akira Kawakami's one-man loincloth girl show.
Thank you very much.
How was it? What did you think?
Well, it was fun.
It was my first time to appear on "Hitori Fundoshi" and I was a little nervous because it was a live broadcast,
I was a little nervous because it was a live broadcast.
But I was very happy to be able to perform with Aika-chan and tell everyone about the charm of the live performance.
Thank you very much.
It was my first time to perform, so I was really stiff and I was really good,
I was really good, but at the end I had to make funny faces, and I was able to stay true to myself until the end,
I was able to convey my charm, and I was happy to be able to tell a good story.
Thank you very much.
Actually, I asked one question in the latter half of the program, a special question,
You both talked a lot, so I have yet to ask a question that I couldn't ask in the program,
Since both of you talked a lot, I have a couple of questions that I couldn't answer in the program.
I would like to ask you to answer a couple of them.
May I ask for your permission?
Yes, I have two questions that were not answered in the program.
That is the first question.
Thank you very much.
A story of failure on stage.
Here it comes.
Okay, let's start with Ms. Tane.
I had an SE that started out with a rhythm, and then I went to the center of the stage and posed,
I was on a big stage at that time.
So I didn't know when to go out on stage first, and I went out at the usual time,
I didn't know when to go out on stage first, so I went out at the usual time and didn't make it in time to strike a pose at the center of the stage,
I was so embarrassed and it was a failure.
Thank you very much.
After that, I started to ask the members to push me to come out.
Next, Erika.
I'm also on stage,
I have a great dance song that I can say is the best in the new sound,
I was still shaking and nervous after the second or third time of spreading the song,
I was in the middle of the stage, and I had to do the dance part,
I was so nervous that I blew up the microphone,
It went off.
Afterwards, I apologized to the PA and cried when I got home,
I went home and cried.
I was so sorry to the PA, and I went home and cried.
The PA would have sent it to me.
I swear I will never drop it. I am so sorry.
Thank you very much.
It was a pretty serious mistake, wasn't it?
Okay, I'll go on to the next question.
I suddenly have tomorrow off. What will you do?
I'm going to eat yakiniku.
I already wanted to eat it before I asked you if I was going to eat it in the first place.
I really wanted to eat.
I'm going to eat as much yakiniku as I want with the members and eat as much as I want.
That sounds good.
Okay, Ayaka.
I'll sleep as much as I can,
I want to sleep as much as I can, and then go out for ramen and coke, my favorite food, late at night.
I would get fat.
I love ramen and Coke more than anything else in the world,
The combination?
Yes. But it's a big calorie-backload,
I was told by the members that I should stop eating ramen about halfway through this month,
I'm on a ban right now, but I'm going to Fukuoka next month,
I'm going to Fukuoka next month.
Now I would like to go to the last question.
What is your favorite food?
Ramen and cola!
I like beef tongue.
Beef tongue.
I love beef tongue.
I understand. I eat it the most.
But as we were talking earlier, we both love Coke,
Only Coca-Cola.
No Zero.
Not even Rockin' Pepper.
Really Coca-Cola.
But some of our fans say it's too sweet and they can't drink it.
It's definitely Coca-Cola.
If you can't taste this flavor, you still seem to be halfway through life.
But I've never had ramen and Coke.
You should definitely do it.
Please do it because it will really revolutionize your life.
I understand.
Yaki Ramen and Coke is the best?
Tonkotsu (pork bone).
The first time I went to Fukuoka on an expedition, I ate ramen there,
It was really shocking and too delicious.
Let's go there.
It was ramen and Coke, wasn't it?
Coca-Cola's regular Coke.
I'll do it.
I'll go back and do it too.
Thank you very much.
Once again, I have been invited to appear on Volume 2 of Tokyo Yakan Land,
I was also able to perform in a live one-man loincloth show,
I hope that the charm of my main live performance will be conveyed to many of you.
Thank you very much.
Today was my first time to perform, and I was very nervous,
I was very excited to perform for the first time today, but in the end I was very happy to be able to speak to you with a smile and my true self,
I hope that both Ms. Kawakami and Mr. Takatani will continue to see Theon make great strides in the future,I hope that both Mr. Kawakami and Mr. Takatani will continue to see Theon make great strides in the future,
I will continue to do my best for Theon, and I hope you all will keep an eye on Theon without missing a beat.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Well, thank you very much for today.
Bye-bye.